gracessweetlife.com 2013-11-09

# Privacy Policy for the Grace's Sweet Life Website

## **Privacy Policy**

 _ **Last Updated: February 19, 2013**_

 **Grace’s Sweet Life  **is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This privacy policy tells you about the information we collect on our Website and how we use that information. By using the  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  Website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy, which may be modified from time to time by us.

##  **Children Under 13:**

We care about protecting the privacy of children. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).

##  **Information We Collect:**

The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) information you supply when you register to receive emails or comment on the Website, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our Website.

###  **Personally Identifying Information**

In operating the Website,  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  may include registration, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, email addresses, and other contact information.

###  **Tracking Information**

 **Cookies**. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Website. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our Website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on you browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Website may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

 **Click Tracking**. As is true of most websites,  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically collected data to personal information.

 **IP Addresses**. Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on  **Grace’s Sweet Life**. This information is never provided to the third parties, except as otherwise stated in this  **Privacy Policy** , and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to personal information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Website.

 **Advertising**. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  **Google** , as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  **Grace’s Sweet Life**.  **Google’s  **use of the  **DART cookie  **enables it to serve ads based on your visit to the  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  Website and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the  **Dart cookie  **by visiting the  **[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ "Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy ")**.

 **Third-Party Ad Servers or Ad Networks**. The third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on the  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  Website, which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  Website.

 **Grace’s Sweet Life**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Our advertising partners include:

Martha’s Circle through DoubleClick by Google

Google AdSense

 **[DoubleClick Cookies](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090?hl=en "DoubleClick Cookies") **explained.

 **Google Advertising Cookies**. You can use the [ **Ads Preferences Manager**](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjSL-S9tc5MabfPMDMSu4bG3JN6l68DvhNhApaLVghje5Q-SElQsBUbB-wG8eLCD4ycqNaH0CN3vtzolPvAD8cVW36um2JttuEUPE38KKxwDQZL1dUKe8CWvoztHpX3uZoIcXpYchcz_O1Gbhxc2D6noSFnwkBotVcBMat4HgiUxmO4Ts3yWl3LwEYh8y22QvWn08rdruJ40FgHksvpELCwipJMUg "Google Ads Preferences Manager") to manage the ads you see.

 **Manage/Opt-Out Third-Party Cookies**. You can manage many companies’ cookies used for online advertising at the [ **Network Advertising Initiative**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Opt-Out/Manage Advertising Cookies at Network Advertising Initiative").

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Third Party Privacy Policies**. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. The  **Grace’s Sweet Life’s**   **Privacy Policy**  does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or Websites.

 **Participation on a Public Website**. You should be aware that any personal information you submit on the  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  Website in the comments may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Website, including anonymous visitors.

##  **How Your Information Will Be Used:**

 **Personal Information**. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the  **Grace’s Sweet Life Website** , or to send you additional information about  **Grace’s Sweet Life**.

 **Anonymous Information**. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

 **Use of Cookies**. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

 **Disclosure of Personal Information**. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  (2) protect and defend the rights or property of  **Grace’s Sweet Life**  or the users of this site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this site.

###  **Security**

 **** **Grace’s Sweet Life**  has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

###  **Comments**

 **Grace’s Sweet Life**  may include interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

###  **Third Party Websites**

Grace’s Sweet Life may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

###  **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this policy, our practices related to this site, please feel free to contact us at the following **[privacy@gracessweetlife.com](mailto:privacy@gracessweetlife.com)**.

###  **Updates and Changes**

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy simply by posting such change, update, or modification on  **Grace’s Sweet Life** , and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
